export const reactQuestion = [
    {
        question: "Microsoft Excel is what kind of software?",
        options: [
            "Word Processing Software",
            "Spreadsheet Software",
            "Database Software",
            "Presentation Software"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Spreadsheet Software"
    },
    {
        question: "An Excel file format extension is?",
        options: [
            "doc",
            "xls",
            "txt",
            "mp3"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "xls"
    },
    {
        question: "The numbers in Excel represent the...?",
        options: [
            "Rows",
            "Columns",
            "Cells",
            "Data"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Rows"
    },
    {
        question: "When creating a chart in Excel, what is the first thing you need to do?",
        options: [
            "Select the data to be graphed.",
            "Select the Insert Tab",
            "Choose a chart from the ribbon",
            "Double click the active cell"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Select the data to be graphed."
    },
    {
        question: "To alert Excel that you are entering a formula and not text, type a(n) ____________ preceding the formula.",
        options: [
            "&",
            "=",
            "#",
            "*"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "="
    },
    {
        question: "What function adds all of the numbers in a range of cells?",
        options: [
            "Calculate",
            "Compute",
            "Sum",
            "Max"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Sum"
    },
    {
        question: "To sort data in Excel, go to the __________ ribbon.",
        options: [
            "Home",
            "Data",
            "Insert",
            "View"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Home"
    },
    {
        question: "What does the mouse look like in a spreadsheet?",
        options: [
            "Arrow",
            "Two headed arrow",
            "Pointer",
            "Selection cross"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Selection cross"
    },
    {
        question: "If I want to find an average of cells A1 through A25, which formula would I use?",
        options: [
            "=average(A1:A25)",
            "=avg(A1:A25)",
            "=average(A1-A25)",
            "=avg(A1-A25)"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "=average(A1:A25)"
    },
    {
        question: "Alex needs to add three cells and then divide the sum by 4. Which of the following is an example of the correct formula to do this? ",
        options: [
            "=(A1+A2+A3)/4",
            "A1+A2+A3/4",
            "=A1+A2+A3^4",
            "(A1+A2) + A3/4"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "=(A1+A2+A3)/4"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following methods cannot be used to enter data in a cell",
        options: [
            "a. Pressing an arrow key",
            "b. Pressing the Tab key",
            "c. Pressing the Esc key",
            "d. Clicking on the formula bar"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "c. Pressing the Esc key"
    },
    {
        question: "When a label is too long to fit within a worksheet cell, you typically must",
        options: [
            "a. Shorten the label",
            "b. Increase the column width",
            "c. Decrease the column width",
            "d. Adjust the row height"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "b. Increase the column width"
    },
    {
        question: "In MS-Excel numeric value can be treated as a label value if it precedes with",
        options: [
            "A. Apostrophe (')",
            "B. Exclamation (!)",
            "C. Hash (#)",
            "D. None of these"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "A. Apostrophe (')"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the shortcut key to hide entire column?",
        options: [
            "A. CTRL + ",
            "B. CTRL + 0",
            "C. CTRL + H",
            "D. CTRL + C"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "B. CTRL + 0"
    },
    {
        question: "The advantage of using a spreadsheet is:",
        options: [
            "A. calculations can be done automatically.",
            "B. changing data automatically updates calculations",
            "C. more flexibility",
            "D. All of the above"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "D. All of the above"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Microsoft Excel?",
        options: [
            "Writer",
            "Spreadsheet",
            "Operating System",
            "Presenter"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Spreadsheet"
    },
    {
        question: "The letters in Excel represent the...",
        options: [
            "Rows",
            "Columns",
            "Cells",
            "Data"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Columns"
    },
    {
        question: "The intersection of a row and column.",
        options: [
            "column",
            "row",
            "cell",
            "active cell"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "cell"
    },
    {
        question: "What makes up a spreadsheet?",
        options: [
            "rows and commands",
            "rows and columns",
            "rolls and columns",
            "rose and columns"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "rows and columns"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a small rectangular box in a spreadsheet called?",
        options: [
            "column",
            "prison",
            "cell",
            "cage"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "cell"
    }
];